Punk Music Library PUNK007
People's Archive, MLK Library
Punk Music Library Collection
Undated
People's Archive, MLK Library
PUNK007
19 Boxes
- Series 1: 12"
  - Bad Brains - Bad Brains (Label: Rior), Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 9353 - We Are Absolutely Sure There is No God (Label: Fountain of Youth), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    FOYO15
  - Beatnik Flies - From Parts Unknown (Label: Dacoit), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1002
  - Insect Surfers - Sonar Safari (Label: Wasp), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Insect Surfers - Wavelength (Label: Wasp ), 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sting 14ep
  - Worlds Collide - Worlds Collide (Label: Get Ross! Live 3/20/92), Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chain and the Gang - In Cool Blood (Label: K Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chain and the Gang - Music's Not for Everyone (Label: K Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    klp220
  - Chain and the Gang - Minimum Rock N Roll (Label: Radical Elite Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    RE 001
  - Ex Hex - Rips (Label: Merge), 2014 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Priests - Bodies and Control and Money and Power (Label: Don Giovanni Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chalk Circle - Reflection (Label: Mississippi Records/Post Present Medium), 1981-83/2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    MR069-PPM 040
  - Diamond District - March on Washington (Label: Mello Music Group), 2014 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    LP-MMGO57
  - King Face - King Face (Label: self-released), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    n/a
  - Fugazi - Fugazi (Label: Dischord Records), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    30
  - Rites of Spring - Rites of Spring (Label: Dischord Records), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    16
  - Various Artists - Flex Your Head (Label: Dischord Records), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    7
  - Vile Cherubs - Post-Humorous Relief (Label: Dischord Records / Cherubic Delusions), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    33 1/3; 3
  - Fugazi - Repeater (Label: Dischord Records), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    44
  - Madhouse - Madhouse (Label: Fountain of Youth Records), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    012
  - Soulside - Less Deep Inside Keeps (Label: Dischord Records / Sammich Records), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    22 1/2; 2
  - Autoclave - Autoclave (Label: Dischord Records / Mira Records), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    65 1/2; 1
  - Faith - Subject to Change (Label: Dischord Records), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    11
  - Minor Threat - Minor Threat (Label: Discord Records), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    12
  - Soulside - Less Deep Inside Keeps (Label: Dischord/Sammich), Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Soulside - Trigger (Label: Dischord), Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    DIS179V
  - 9353 - To Whom it May Consume, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 9353 - We Are Absolutely Sure There is No God, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Beefeater - Plays For Lovers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bouncing Babies - Bouncing Babies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Crippled Pilgrims - Head Down, Handout, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Crippled Pilgrims - Under Water, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Minor Threat - Two 7" EPs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minor Threat - Out of Step, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rites of Spring - Rites of Spring, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tommy Keene - Back Again (Try...), Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Tommy Keene - Based on Happy times, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Tommy Keene - Places That Are Gone, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Tommy Keene - Run Now, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tommy Keene - Songs From the Film, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Tommy Keene - Strange Alliance, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Urban Verbs - Urban Verbs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Urban Verbs - Early Damage, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Various Artists - Connected, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Various Artists - Flex Your Head, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Various Artists - Four Old 7" on a 12", Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mobius Strip - Escalate, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mobius Strip - A Knee in the Back, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fidelity Jones - Piltdown Lad, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Del Cielo - This is the First Album by Del Cielo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Trophy Wife - Patience Fury, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Trophy Wife - Sing What Scares You, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Turboslut/Pygmy Lush - Split, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Police and Theives - Fracturing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Worn Thin - Long Road Ahead, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Fire Party - 6 Songs (Label: Dischord Records), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    DIS28
  - Fire Party - New Orleans Opera (Label: Dischord Records), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    DIS37
  - Fugazi - 7 Songs (Label: Dischord Records), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    DIS30V
  - Fugazi - Margin Walker (Label: Dischord Records), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    DIS35V
  - Minor Threat - First 2 7"s (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Minor Threat - Out Of Step (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bad Brains - S/t (Label: Roir), Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bikini Kill - S/t (Label: Bikini Kill Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bikini Kill - Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah (Label: Bikini Kill Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chain and the Gang - Minimum Rock N Roll (Label: Radical Elite Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chain and the Gang - Music's Not For Everyone (Label: K Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cigarette - Gush (Label: PHAEDRA RECORDS), Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dag Nasty - Can I Say (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dag Nasty - Dag with Shawn (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dag Nasty - Wig Out At Denko's (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Darkest Hour - The Human Man (Label: ORG Music), 2011 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    ORGM-1042
  - Del Cielo - Wish And Wait (Label: Exotic Fever), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    EXF 13/GB 05
  - E.D. Sedgwick - We Wear White (Label: Dischord Records), 2012 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    DIS175V
  - El Guapo - Fake French (Label: Dischord Records), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    DIS134V
  - Embrace - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    DIS24V
  - Evens, The - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    DIS150V
  - Evens, The - The Odds (Label: Dischord Records), 2012 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    DIS180V
  - Faith Void - Split (Label: Dischord Records), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    DIS8
  - Faraquet - The View From This Tower (Label: Dischord Records), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    DIS122V
  - Fort Knox Five - Radio Free DC (Label: Fort Knox Recordings), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    FKX-012
  - Fugazi - End Hits (Label: Dischord Records), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    DIS110V
  - Fugazi - In On The Killtaker (Label: Dischord Records), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    DIS70V
  - Fugazi - Instrument Soundtrack (Label: Dischord Records), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    DIS120V
  - Fugazi - Red Medicine (Label: Dischord Records), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    DIS90V
  - Fugazi - Repeater (Label: Dischord Records), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    DIS44V
  - Fugazi - The Argument (Label: Dischord Records), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    DIS130V
  - All Scars - Introduction to Humanity (Label: Slowdime), Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Apes, The - Street Warz (Label: Planaria), Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Artificial Peace - Complete Session Nov 81 (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Black Eyes - Cough (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Black Eyes - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Deathfix - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Evens, The - Get Evens (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Faith - Subject to Change plus First Demo (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Fugazi - Steady Diet Of Nothing (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Gift, The - Mostly In Sickness (Label: Amor Y Lucha Records), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Government Issue - Joy Ride (Label: Doctor Strange Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    DSR-121
  - Government Issue - The Fun Just Never Ends (Label: Doctor Strange Records), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    DSR-123
  - Gray Matter - Food For Thought (Label: Dischord Records), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    DIS48
  - Gray Matter - Take It Back and 4 (Label: Dischord Records), 1985/1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    DIS21
  - Heavy Breathing - Body Problems (Label: Glove Music), 2012 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    2
  - High Back Chairs - Of Two Minds (Label: Dischord Records), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    DIS56V
  - Holy Rollers - As Is (Label: Dischord Records), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    DIS42
  - Holy Rollers - Fabuley (Label: Dischord Records), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    DIS58V
  - Holy Rollers - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    DIS86V
  - Hoover - The Lurid Traversal of Route 7 (Label: Dischord Records), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    DIS89V
  - Jawbox - For Your Own Special Sweetheart (Label: Desoto Records), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    JA53
  - Jawbox - Grippe (Label: Dischord Records), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    DIS52
  - Jawbox - Novelty (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    DIS69V
  - Lungfish - ACR 1999 (Label: Dischord Records) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Lungfish - Indivisble (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Make Up - Destination: Love Live! At Cold Rice (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Make Up - In Mass Mind (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Make Up, The - I Want Some (Label: M'Lady's Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Medications - Completely Removed (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Janel and Anthony - 5th Anniversary (Label: Cricket Cemetery), 2012 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    CCO12
  - Lungfish - Pass And Stow (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lungfish - Talking Songs For Walking (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Lungfish - The Unanimous Hour (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nation of Ulysses - 13 Point Program to Destroy America (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nation of Ulysses - Plays Pretty For Baby (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - New Wet Kojak - 12" Remix (Label: Akashic ), Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - One Last Wish - 1986 (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Orthrelm - 2nd 18/04 (Label: Three One G), Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Passing Phases - Endless Autumn (Label: Cricket Cemetery), Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Pizza - Midnight Creature Party (Label: Sterling Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - points - s/t (Label: Mud Memory), Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Protect U - Free USA (Label: Future Times), Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pygmy Lush - Mt Hope (Label: Lovitt Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pygmy Lush - Old Friends (Label: Lovitt Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Q and Not U - Different Damage (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Q and Not U - No Kill No Beep Beep (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Red Hare - Nites of Midnite (Label: Dischord Half Label), 2013 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    180.5
  - Rites Of Spring - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Scream - Still Screaming (Label: Dischord Records), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    9
  - Sunwolf - Angel Eyes (Label: El Ray), 2013 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    SUN002
  - Tender Thrills - S/t (Label: Cricket Cemetery), 2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    CC#004
  - Tereu Tereu - All That Keeps Us Together (Label: Self Released), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Three - Dark Days Coming (Label: Dischord Records), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    33
  - Title Tracks - It Was Easy (Label: Earnest Jennings), 2010 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    EJRC062
  - Trophy Wife - Sing What Scares (Label: 307 Knox), Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    307041
  - Two Inch Astronaut - Bad Brother (Label: Exploding Into Sound), 2013 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    EIS-007
  - Void - Sessions 81-83 (Label: Dischord Records), 2011 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    DIS171V
  - Ris Paul Ric - Purple Blaze (Label: Academy Fight Song), Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Rites Of Spring - Six Song Demo (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Various Artists - Flex Your Head (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 9353 - To Whom it May Consume, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Battery - Let The Past Go, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Battery - Whatever it Takes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Black Market Baby - Baby on Board, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Braille Party - Welcome to Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cold Cold Hearts, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Crippled Pilgrims - Head Down Head Out, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - D.O.C. - Decomposition, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Desperate Measures - Never Enough Time, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fordists - Watch You, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Girl Loves Distortion - You Better Run, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Government Issue - Give Us Stabb, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Lion of Judah - Universal Peace, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Majority Rule - Emergency Numbers, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Manifesto - History, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Scream - This Side Up!, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Second Wind - Security, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Soulside - Less Deep/Inside Keeps, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Sweetbelly Freakdown/Bluetip/Kerosene/454/Naht - split, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Tennis System - Teenagers, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Tommy Keene - Back Again, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - White Boy - Kissing After, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Worlds Collide - All Hope Abandon, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Worlds Collide - Get Ross! Live, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Bad Brains - Spirit Electricity Live (Label: SST), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Beaver - s/t (Label: Dr. Strange Records (Reissue)), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    130
  - Beefeater - Need a Job (Label: Olive Tree/Beefeater), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    EP106
  - Bloody Mannequin Orchestra - Roadmap to Revolution (Label: WGNS/EPU ), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chalk Circle - Reflection (Label: Mississippi Records/Post Present Medium (Reissue)), 1981-1983, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    069/040
  - Coke Bust - Confined (Label: Grave Mistake Records), 2013 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    067
  - Crispus Attucks - Red Black Blood Attack, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dismemberment Plan - Emergency and I (Label: Barsuk Records), Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Evens, The - Get Evens, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Foundation - Voyage, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Government Issue - Live, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Government Issue - s/t, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Government Issue - You, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Madhouse - s/t, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Majority Rule - Interviews with David Frost, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Make Up - Save Yourself (Label: K Records), Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Marginal Man - Identity (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Max Levine Ensemble, The - Mr Gikokovich 2000-2005 A Retrospective, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Robert Gordon w Link Wray -, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Root Boy Slim and the Sex Change Band with the Rootettes - S/T (Label: Warner Brothers), Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Shirks, The - s/t, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Slickee Boys - Here to Stay/Porcelain Butter Kitten (Label: Dacoit), Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Spoonboy - I Love You This is a Robbery, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Time Machine, The - Recorded Live at the Back Alley, Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Tru Fax and the Insaniacs - Mental Decay (Label: Wasp), Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Urban Verbs - s/t, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Various Artists - Connected (Label: Limp), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    1005
  - Velocity Girl - Copacetic, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Misled Youth - S/T (Label: Society Bleeds Records/Refuse Records), Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Series 2: 7"
  - Coup Sauvage and the Snips - Sneaks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Berman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blast Off Country Style - I Love Entertainment (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Young Caucasians and The Serfs - Get Going (Label: Go Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bratmobile - Kiss and Ride (Label: Homestead), Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Strange Boutique - A Song From Under the Floorboards (Label: Yesterday and Today), Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mother May I - In a Box (Label: Dat Kord), Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Graverobbers - Justine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graverobbers - Mark Robinson (Label: Homestead), Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Obangis - Lovesick (Label: Deceased), Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mark Noone - Surf Single (Label: Midnight), Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Puppets - Look at the Girls (Label: Parade), Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - French are From Hell - Gunfight (Label: Bavaria France), Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Slickee Boys - Long Way to Go (Label: DeCeased), Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - High Back Chairs - Share (Label: Dischord), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Unrest - Isabel Bishop (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Tsunami - Geniuses of Crack (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Grenadine - Fillings and Gillian (Label: Teenbeat/Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Unrest - Bavarian Mods and other hits (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Unrest - Cherry Cherry (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Unrest - Yes She is my Skinhead Girl (Label: K), Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Eggs - Skyscraper (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Various - Screw (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Various - Lever (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Various - Pulley (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - choke - Kingdom of Mattresess (Label: Vermin Scum/simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Tsunami - Flameproof Suit (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Severin - Fire and Sand (Label: Superbad/Dischord), Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Acrylix - Waiting in the Car (Label: Chichi), Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Velocity Girl - My Forgotten Favorite (Label: Slumberland ), Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Black Tambourine - By Tomorrow (Label: Slumberland ), Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Various - Neopolitan Metropolitan (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ex Hex - Hot and Cold (Label: Merge Record), Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mobius Strip - Palabras Pordrias (Label: Crooked Beat Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Insurgence DC - True to Life (Label: Crooked Beat Records), Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Loud Boyz - Hard Feelings (Label: Cricket Cemetery), Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Various - Neopolitan Metropolitan (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Telegraph Melts - Heiligeschichte und Weltgeschichte, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Various - Screw (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Scream - Walking by Myself (Label: Jungle Hop), Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Shudder to Think - It Was Arson (Label: Dischord/Sammich), Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fugazi - 3 Songs (Label: Dischord ), Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Egg Hunt - Me and You (Label: Dischord), Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mobius Strip - Palabras Pordrias (Label: Crooked Beat), Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mobius Strip - Step Down (Label: Left Out), Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Slickee Boys - Hot and Cool (Label: Dacoit), Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Good Clean Fun - Shopping For a Crew (Label: Reflections), Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Andrea Lisi - Strangers (Label: Exotic Fever ), Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Evens - Warble Factor (Label: Dischord), Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fordists - Economic Stimulus, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fordists - Post-Structuralist Goes to Washington, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ignition - Sinker, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Whorl - Mind Revolution (Label: Slumberland), Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Antimony - Red Herring (Label: Dischord Records/Regulus), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    94.5/ 51
  - Bikini Kill - New Radio, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bikini Kill - Peel Sessions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bratmobile/Veronica Lake - May, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Circus Lupus - A New Goal, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Crownhate Ruin - Primer, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cupid Car Club - join our club (Label: kill rock stars), Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Desiderata - Walking in my Sleep (Label: Dischord Records), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    61.5
  - Double-O - You've Lost (Label: Dischord Records/ Rand B records), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    1/ 10 1/2
  - Egghunt - Me and You (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fugazi - 3 Songs (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Fury - Resurrection, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hoover - Return, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hoover - Sidecar Freddie (Label: Dischord Records / Hoover Limited), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    79.5 / 1
  - Hoover/Lincoln - Two Sided Coin, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Jawbox - Tools and Chrome (Label: Dischord Records/ Desoto), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    45 1/2
  - Lunchmeat/Mission Impossible - Thanks, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Minor Threat - Salad Days (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - MMR - Zusammen, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Nurses, The - Hearts/Cardiac Arrest (Label: Round Raoul), Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Rain Like the Sound of Trains - Incoming, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Sea Tiger - Sea Tiger Theme Song, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sevens - 777, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Sevens - This Side, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Slickee Boys - Mersey Mersey Me (Label: Limp), Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Sorts, The - How Did You Get There, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Soulside - Bass 103, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Suture - Good Girl, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Tsunami - Flameproof Suit, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - United Mutation - Fugitive Family (Label: DSI / Dischord), Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Various Artists - Wedge, Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Velocity Girl - I Don't Care if You Go, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Velocity Girl - My Forgotten Favorite, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Void - Condensed Flesh, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - White Boy - Heavens of Hell, Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - White Boy - I Could Puke / Disco Elephant (Label: Doodley Squat), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Whorl - Maybe It's Better, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Whorl - Mind Revolution, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Various - Vehicle (Label: Shute), Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State Funeral - Protest Music (Label: Artcore), Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Edsel - My Manacles (Label: DeSoto), Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Police and Theives - Amor Y Guerra (Label: Youngblood), Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Worn Thin - Remnants of What Could Have Been (Label: Youngblood), Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Worn Thin - Time's Up (Label: Malfunction), Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Police and Theives/Remission - Split (Label: Amendment), Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Police and Theives - Harbors (Label: Higher Conscience), Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Apes, The - Bodies (Label: Windian Records), 2014 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    20039
  - Apes, The - Luv is Real (Label: Self Released), Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)